http://www.coophousing.org/terms-of-service

Terms of Service
By using this website, you agree to the following terms of service.
This website (including, but not limited to, text, content, graphics, video, and audio) is protected by copyright as a collective work or compilation under U.S. copyright and other laws. Any unauthorized republication or redistribution is strictly prohibited. You may, however, create links to any URL on this website without receiving prior permission.
Information on this website is provided “as is” without any warranty of any kind, either express or implied, including, but not limited to, the implied warranties of merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose, or non-infringement. We do not warrant that service will be uninterrupted or error-free. Some jurisdictions do not allow the exclusion of implied warranties, so the above exclusion may not apply to you.
Information on this website may contain technical inaccuracies or typographical errors. Information may be changed or updated at any time and without notice. The National Association of Housing Cooperatives (NAHC) may also make improvements and/or changes in the products and/or programs described in this information at any time and without notice.
NAHC makes no representations whatsoever about any other website which you may access through this one. When you access a non-NAHC website, please understand that it is independent of NAHC, and that NAHC has no control over the availability of or content on that website. In addition, a link to a non-NAHC website does not mean that NAHC endorses or accepts any responsibility for the content, or the use, of such website. It is up to you to take precautions to ensure that whatever you select for your use is free of such items as viruses, worms, trojan horses, and other items of a destructive nature. In no event will NAHC be liable to any party for any direct, indirect, special or other consequential damages for any use of this website, or on any other hyperlinked website, including, without limitation, any lost profits, business interruption, loss of programs or other data on your information handling system or otherwise, even if we are expressly advised of the possibility of such damages.
This website contains information about programs, products, services and publications offered by third parties, as well as links to third party website. The presence of such a listing or such information does not constitute an endorsement by NAHC of a particular company or organization, or its programs, services, products or publications.
Privacy Policy
The National Association of Housing Cooperatives (NAHC) recognizes the importance of protecting the privacy of its website users. Please read the NAHC privacy policy below:
NAHC is committed to protecting your privacy. Any personal information that you provide to the NAHC should be done by you on a completely voluntary basis. We only use the information you voluntarily provide to process your requests and/or to provide you with additional information about the organization and its programs, services and publications. In addition, we compile aggregate statistics about traffic on our website for internal use only.
Please keep in mind that whenever you provide personal information online, there is a risk that it may be collected and used by people you don’t know. Although NAHC strives to protect the personal information of its website users, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you disclose online and you do so at your own risk.
The NAHC may release personal information when it believes, in good faith, that such release is reasonably necessary to comply with the law, enforce or apply the terms of any of its agreements, or protect the rights or safety of the NAHC, its website users or others.
By using this website, you consent to this NAHC privacy policy. If you do not agree, you should immediately exit this site.
About NAHC
Who We Are
History of NAHC
Latest News
NAHC Board of Directors
Committees & Chairs
Member Associations
Bylaws
Terms of Service
By using this website, you agree to the following terms of service.
This website (including, but not limited to, text, content, graphics, video, and audio) is protected by copyright as a collective work or compilation under U.S. copyright and other laws. Any unauthorized republication or redistribution is strictly prohibited. You may, however, create links to any URL on this website without receiving prior permission.
Information on this website is provided “as is” without any warranty of any kind, either express or implied, including, but not limited to, the implied warranties of merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose, or non-infringement. We do not warrant that service will be uninterrupted or error-free. Some jurisdictions do not allow the exclusion of implied warranties, so the above exclusion may not apply to you.
Information on this website may contain technical inaccuracies or typographical errors. Information may be changed or updated at any time and without notice. The National Association of Housing Cooperatives (NAHC) may also make improvements and/or changes in the products and/or programs described in this information at any time and without notice.
NAHC makes no representations whatsoever about any other website which you may access through this one. When you access a non-NAHC website, please understand that it is independent of NAHC, and that NAHC has no control over the availability of or content on that website. In addition, a link to a non-NAHC website does not mean that NAHC endorses or accepts any responsibility for the content, or the use, of such website. It is up to you to take precautions to ensure that whatever you select for your use is free of such items as viruses, worms, trojan horses, and other items of a destructive nature. In no event will NAHC be liable to any party for any direct, indirect, special or other consequential damages for any use of this website, or on any other hyperlinked website, including, without limitation, any lost profits, business interruption, loss of programs or other data on your information handling system or otherwise, even if we are expressly advised of the possibility of such damages.
This website contains information about programs, products, services and publications offered by third parties, as well as links to third party website. The presence of such a listing or such information does not constitute an endorsement by NAHC of a particular company or organization, or its programs, services, products or publications.
Privacy Policy
The National Association of Housing Cooperatives (NAHC) recognizes the importance of protecting the privacy of its website users. Please read the NAHC privacy policy below:
NAHC is committed to protecting your privacy. Any personal information that you provide to the NAHC should be done by you on a completely voluntary basis. We only use the information you voluntarily provide to process your requests and/or to provide you with additional information about the organization and its programs, services and publications. In addition, we compile aggregate statistics about traffic on our website for internal use only.
Please keep in mind that whenever you provide personal information online, there is a risk that it may be collected and used by people you don’t know. Although NAHC strives to protect the personal information of its website users, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you disclose online and you do so at your own risk.
The NAHC may release personal information when it believes, in good faith, that such release is reasonably necessary to comply with the law, enforce or apply the terms of any of its agreements, or protect the rights or safety of the NAHC, its website users or others.
By using this website, you consent to this NAHC privacy policy. If you do not agree, you should immediately exit this site.
#16 (no title)
Copyright © 2020, National Association of Housing Cooperatives. All rights reserved. Terms of Service | Site by Chrein.com.
